<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NSON</string>
    <string name="description">Nigeria School Of Nursing Entrance Exam Past Questions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "BRIEF OVERVIEW OF NURSING PROFESSION.\n\n"

        "\n Nursing is a profession within the health sector with particular attention on the on the care of individuals, families and community so they may attain, maintain or recover optimal health and quality of life \n "
        "Nurses may be differentiated by their approach to patient care, training and scope of practice \n\n "


        "19th century Florence Nightingale laid the foundation of professional nursing during the Creamean war. "
        "The Nightingale model of professional education, having set up the first school of Nursing  "
        "that is connected to a continuously operated Hospital and medical school spread widely "
        "in Europe and North America after 1870. \n\n "


        "Other important Nurses in the development of the profession include;\n\n"

        "* Agnes Hunt from Shropshire, 1st orthopaedic nurse and pivotal in the emergency of the orthopaedic hospital \n\n "

        "* Agnes Elizabeth Jones and Linda Richards who established quality nursing schools in the United States Of America and Japan \n\n"

        "* Saint Marianne Cope, a sister of St. Francis who opened and operated some of the first general hospital in the United State\n\n "

        "* Catholic orders such as little sisters of the poor, sisters of mercy, sisters of St.Mary e.t.c \n\n"


        "Formal use of Nurses in the modern military began in the later half of the nineteenth century.  "
        "Nurses saw active duty in the FIRST Boer war, the Egyptian campaign 1882 and the Sudan campaign "
        "and in 20th century, many Nurses saw active duty in World war 1".


        ""


    </string>


    <string name="rules_text">
        "Mathematics rules\n\n"

        "capital X = Multiply  eg. " 2X2=4" \n"

        "small x is same as x eg.  "2x+3x+4x = 9x" \n"

        "Raised to power is ^  eg "2^2 = 4, 3^2+3^3 = 36".\n\n"


        "Note \n\n"

        "All questions are solved and checked correctly.\n\n"

        "We added only 50 questions to each categories because scientifically by study it was discovered that too many questions to solve is boring and time consuming, \n\n"
       " but if you need us to add more questions you can drop a feed back and we will add more questions. There are thousands of questions for each categories at hand both in the app and in pdf form\n\n"

        "Questions are extracted from the following Nigeria school of nursing past entrance exam questions \n\n"

        "1. SCHOOL OF NURSING, OGBOMOSHO\n"
        "2. SCHOOL OF NURSING, OSHOGBO\n"
        "3. ECWA SCHOOL OF NURSING, EGBA\n"
        "4. ONDO STATE SCHOOL OF NURSING AND MIDWIFERY, AKURE\n"
        "5. FCT SCHOOL OF NURSING\n"
        "6. SCHOOL OF NURSING, LAGOS UNIVERSITY TEACHING HOSPITAL (LUTH)\n"
        "7. SCHOOL OF NURSING, OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY TEACHING HOSPITAL\n"
        "8. OYO STATE COLLEGE OF NURSING AND MIDWIFERY\n"
        "9. SCHOOL OF NURSING, JOINT HOSPITAL, MBANO ETC.\n\n"


        "Also   The National Council Licensure Examination (NCLEX-RN® exam) exam past questions application us under development and should be deployed soon. This will be  bonus  %of  to subscribers and we will  guide you through it. \n\n\n"

         "Your feedback will make our work great and good \n\n"
        " Monthly update will be perform and to keep you all up to date with the current questions \n\n"

        "Wish you success and all the best\n"

       " Thanks."



    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>